RG 005:033, Office of the Governor: Abraham Ribicoff (1955-1961)
Connecticut State Library
- Series 3. Flood of 1955 Files
  - Flood: Report of Merchants Disaster Committee of Conn[ecticut] to Sherman R. Knapp, Chairman of the Connecticut River Flood Recovery Committee, 1956 February 13 (Box 685)
  - Flood: Public Works Committee, U.S. Senate – Statement by Governor Ribicoff re: Flood Control Projects, 1955 July 16 (Box 685)
  - Flood: Governor’s Emergency Flood Recovery Committee (Box 685)
  - Flood: Flood – Knapp Committee, 2 folders (Box 685)
  - Flood: Connecticut Flood Recovery Commission, Sherman R. Knapp, Chairman (Box 685)
  - Flood: Material: Miscellaneous – Reports on Gov[ernor]’s Visits to Areas, Reports from Various State Agencies, etc. (Box 685)
  - Flood: Frederick P. Clark – Town Planning Consultant (Box 685)
  - Flood: Connecticut Flood Recovery Committee, 1955 (Box 685)
  - Flood: S. 3272: Flood Control Bill in 84th Congress 2nd Session: Senator Prescott Bush (Box 686)
  - Flood: S. 414 and S. 524 Flood Control (Box 686)
  - Flood: Statement by Governor Ribicoff to Appropriation Committee, U.S. Congress, March 19 and 20, 1956 re: Flood Control (Box 686)
  - Flood: Flood Control: Statement by Governor Ribicoff to Public Works Committee U.S. Senate, 1956 March 22 (Box 686)
  - Flood: Report to the State Highway Department on the Rehabilitation of Flood Damaged Locally Maintained Highways and Bridges by Ellis E. Paul, Howard, Needles, Tammen & Bergendoff Consulting Engineers, 1959 July 1 (Box 686)
  - Flood: Flood Damaged and Locally Maintained Highways and Bridges (Box 686)
  - Flood: Report on Disaster – Rehabilitations, Jaycees, February 4, 1956 (Box 686)
  - Flood: U.S. Army Engineers Division, New England, Corps of Engineers, Final Report, 'Operation Noah,', 1958 May (Box 686)
- Series 4. Highway Safety Files
  Contains Highway Safety files that were not included with those folders in the main subject files. The reason for this omission is not known. Researchers will note that the folders generally are alphabetically arranged.
  - Highway Safety Kits (Box 687)
  - [Advisory Council for President’s Committee for Traffic Safety] (Box 687)
  - Aetna Drivotrainer (Box 687)
  - “Aim to Live” – (Harlow Curtice, GM, President) (Box 687)
  - American Ass[ociatio]n of Industrial Nurses Journal Article (Box 687)
  - Anti-Speeding Drive (General) (Box 687)
  - Auto Manufacturers (Box 687)
  - Auto Manufacturers Meeting – Detroit (Box 687)
  - American Weekly “Modest Motorists Stay Alive” (Box 687)
  - Robert Caitlin – Gov[ernor] Ribicoff [newspaper clippings re accusation that Caitlin, chair of the Connecticut Safety Commission, criticized Governor Ribicoff] (Box 687)
  - Awards to Connecticut (Box 687)
  - Traffic Safety Newspaper Clippings, 1960 (Box 687)
  - Clippings, 1960 (Box 687)
  - Clippings – Letters (Box 687)
  - Clippings – General (Box 687)
  - Clippings, 1959 (Box 687)
  - Clippings – Articles (Box 687)
  - Clippings – Editorials (Box 687)
  - Christmas [clippings re: Governor’s message], 1957 (Box 687)
  - C[onnecticut] F[ederation] of L[abor] Stand on Anti-Speeding Drive [clippings], 1956 (Box 687)
  - Congress [report to] (Box 687)
  - Comments on Anti-Speeding Drive (Box 687)
  - Connecticut Safety Commission (Box 687)
  - Conn[ecticut] Speed Survey Coordinating Committee (State) (Box 687)
  - Courts and Legal Profession (Box 687)
  - “Drag” Racing (Box 687)
  - Driver Education (Box 687)
  - The Drivers’ Digest (Article by Ribicoff) (Box 687)
  - Eisenhower Visit, [Ribicoff’s visit to], 1957 June 18 (Box 687)
  - Facts (Box 687)
  - Florida (Box 687)
  - General Assembly, 1957 (Box 687)
  - General Information (Box 687)
  - Governor’s Municipal Police Training (Box 687)
  - Governors’ Conference, Atlantic City, 1956 June (Box 687)
  - Governors’ Conference, Denver, Colorado, Sept[ember], 1956 (Box 687)
  - Governors’ Conference, Williamsburg, V[irgini]a, 1957 June 24 (Box 687)
  - Governors’ Conf[erence] Highway Safety Committee (Box 687)
  - Governors’ Conference Highway Safety Report, 1956 November (Box 687)
  - New Eng[land] Governors’ Conf[erence] (Box 687)
  - Greenwich Crusade for Traffic Safety (Box 687)
  - Guideposts Article (Box 687)
  - Guide Rails (Box 687)
  - Holidays (Box 688)
  - [Holidays] Statement, 1960 July 4 (Box 688)
  - [Holidays] Labor Day Statement, 1960 September 1 (Box 688)
  - The Human Side of Safety, by Louis H. Bornoff [Safety Manager, The H. K. Ferguson Company, Cincinnati, Ohio], 1957 (Box 688)
  - Industrial Plants (Box 688)
  - Kiwanis Clubs (Box 688)
  - Law and Order Magazine – Guest Editorial by Governor Ribicoff (Box 688)
  - Massachusetts (Box 688)
  - Maximum Speed (Box 688)
  - Merritt P[ar]kw[a]y (Box 688)
  - Metropolitan Area Conference, 1957 September 20 (Box 688)
  - Milford Exchange Club, 1958 May 28 (Box 688)
  - Monthly Reports [Department of Motor Vehicles re: accidents and fatalities], 1956-1957 (Box 688)
  - Monthly Statistical Statement of Traffic Fatality Experience [Department of Motor Vehicles] (Box 688)
  - Movietone News [Script for Governor Ribicoff’s narration of the cinemascope highway safety newsreel] (Box 688)
  - National Safety Council (Box 688)
  - New Jersey (Box 688)
  - New York Herald Tribune Question and Answer (Box 688)
  - New York State (Box 688)
  - “No License to Kill” – Alcoa Hour, NBC TV (Box 688)
  - Other States (Box 688)
  - Out-of-State Traffic Flow (Box 688)
  - Poquetanuck Drawbridge (Norwich Bulletin) (Box 688)
  - Posted Speed Limits [press releases] (Box 688)
  - President’s Traffic Safety Committee (Box 688)
  - Readers Digest (Box 688)
  - Regional Traffic Safety Conferences (Box 688)
  - Religious Traffic Safety Weekend (Box 688)
  - Republican Platform on Anti-Speed Drive (Box 688)
  - Rotarian Magazine re: T. E. Murphy’s article on the (Box 688)
  - Connecticut Highway Safety Program (Box 688)
  - Saturday Evening Post article: “Slow Down in Connecticut,” [by Governor Ribicoff] (Box 688)
  - Savage, Henry [suspended license] (Box 688)
  - Schools (Box 688)
  - School Bus Drivers (Box 688)
  - Servicemen (Box 688)
  - Signs at State Lines (Box 688)
  - Speed Study (Box 688)
  - State Police Analysis of Traffic Law Enforcement (Box 688)
  - State Police Survey of Public Opinion (Box 688)
  - Statements and Letters (Box 688)
  - Safety Statistics, 1960 (Box 688)
  - Statistics, 1956-1960 (Box 689)
  - State Government Article, “Highway Safety: Proposals and Performance,” [by Governor Ribicoff] (Box 689)
  - "Management Survey Report, Division of Operator Control, Connecticut Department of Motor Vehicles" by Management Analysis Section, Budget Division, Department of Finance and Control, 1956 July 27; 1 volume (Box 689)
  - Travelers Article, “Bold Action or Reproach?” [By Governor Ribicoff] (Box 689)
  - Triangle Publications Drive (Box 689)
  - Uniform Laws (Box 689)
  - U. S. News [and World Report] [article re: Connecticut’s highway program], 1959 January 30 (Box 689)
  - Vancouver Sun articles (Box 689)
  - Vavin, Inc. (Film Made by Governor Ribicoff), 1958 July 21 (Box 689)
  - WBIS [Bristol] Tape Recording “Walk with Safety” Slogan Contest (Box 689)
  - WDRC Tapes [Made by Governor Ribicoff] (Box 689)
  - Woman’s Day article [About Governor Ribicoff’s Highway Safety Program], 1957 January (Box 689)
  - Yankee Magazine, “Connecticut Clamps Down,” by Jos[eph] A. Owens (Box 689)
- Series 5. Campaign File, 1958
  Files generally contain copies of bills, press releases, reports, and clippings as reference material for use by candidate Ribicoff. Some folders are labeled as "Master File," though the reason for this distinction from other folders in the box is not clear.
  Alphabetical order by subject.
  - Aging - Master Files (Box 690)
  - Agriculture - Master File (Box 690)
  - Conservation - Master File (Box 690)
  - Conservation – Beach Erosion (Box 690)
  - Conservation – Flood Control (Box 690)
  - Education – Master File (Box 690)
  - Education - Clippings (Box 690)
  - Education – Costs to Towns (Box 690)
  - Education – Higher (Box 690)
  - Education – Medical and Dental Schools (Box 690)
  - Education – Miscellaneous (Box 690)
  - Education – Scholarships (Box 690)
  - Education – School Buildings (Proposals, Progress) (Box 690)
  - Education – Secondary and Primary (Box 690)
  - Education – Teachers’ Salaries (Box 690)
  - Education – Technical Schools (Box 690)
  - Education – TV (Box 690)
  - Education – University of Connecticut (Box 690)
  - Education – White House Conference (Box 690)
  - Health – Master File (Box 690)
  - Mental Health – Master File (Box 690)
  - Mentally Retarded – Master File (Box 690)
  - Penal – Master File (Box 690)
  - Water Resources – Master file (Box 690)
  - Welfare – Master File (Box 690)
- Series 6. Appointment Files
  Contains appointments to government posts made by Gov. Ribicoff.
  - Gubernatorial Appointments (Box 691)
  - Appointments by Gov[ernor] Ribicoff to Various Boards, Commissions, etc., 3 folders (Box 691)
  - Appointments to Major Posts – (Biographies) (Box 691)
  - Workman’s Compensation, Commission of (Box 691)
  - Appointments – Made by the Governor, 1957 (Box 691)
  - Direct Appointments to Be Made in 1957 (Box 691)
  - Executive Appointments: for publication in the back of Special Acts, 1957 (Box 691)
  - Complaints: Courts (Box 691)
  - Minor Court: List of Appointments Made February 9, 1959 (Box 691)
  - Probate Courts, 1959 (Box 691)
  - Probate Court Judgeships, 1957 (Box 691)
  - Superior Court, List of names recommended for appointment to (Box 691)
  - Superior Court Recommendations – Judgeships, 1957 (Box 691)
  - Superior Court Judgeships, 1959 (Box 691)
  - Common Pleas Court Recommendations – Judgeships, 1957 (Box 691)
  - Court of Common Pleas or Superior, List of those recommended for appointment to (Box 691)
  - Municipal and Town Courts’ Correspondence relative to appointments made on May 1, 1959 (Box 691)
  - Biographies – Republican Judge Candidates (Box 691)
  - Circuit Courts: Points of view regarding appointments to (Box 691)
  - Circuit Courts: Request for Prosecutor and Clerk Appointments (Box 691)
  - Circuit Court: List of names recommended for appointment (Box 691)
  - Circuit Court: Letters of appreciation from appointed judges and their supporters (Box 691)
  - Circuit Court: Copies of Biographies of Appointed Judges (Box 691)
  - Judicial Appointments: Complete list of appointments made by Governor on May 1, 1959 (Box 691)
  - The following folders are labeled only by the first letter of surname and contain letters from applicants for judicial appointment, biographies and resumes, and letters of support or other opinions.
  - A – J, 10 folders (Box 692)
  - K – Z, 16 folders, half the box (Box 692)
  - Hegstrom, Harold E., Warden [Federal Correctional Institution, Danbury] (Box 692)
  - Appointments – Copies of Press Releases (Box 692)
  - Appointments, Direct and Indirect, Made by Governor, 1955-1957 (Box 692)
  - Commissioners and Department Heads, Correspondence relative to appointments of, 1959 (Box 692)
  - The following files are arranged alphabetically by title of position. Generally they contain letters supporting the proposed appointee or candidate for appointment or suggesting the name or names of persons. The bulk of these files date from 1957 to 1960.
  - Athletic Commissioner (Box 692)
  - Auditor, State of Connecticut (Box 692)
  - Barbers, Examining Board of (Box 692)
  - Blind, Board of Education of the (Box 692)
  - Boxing Commissioner (Box 692)
  - Bridge Commissioner (Box 692)
  - Civil Defense Director (Box 692)
  - Civil War Centennial Commission (Box 692)
  - Consumer Protection Deputy Commissioner (Box 692)
  - County Commissioners (Box 692)
  - Dams and Reservoirs, State Board for the Supervision of (Box 692)
  - Dental Commission (Box 692)
  - Dental Commissioner (Box 692)
  - Development Commission, Connecticut (Box 692)
  - Education, State Board of (Box 692)
  - Embalmers & Funeral Directors, Board of Examiners of (Box 692)
  - Employees’ Retirement Commission, Connecticut (Box 692)
  - Engineers and Land Surveyors, State Board of Registration for (Box 692)
  - Fairfield State Hospital, Trustees of the (Box 692)
  - Fire Safety Commission (Box 692)
  - Fisheries and Game, State Board of (Box 692)
  - Food and Drug Commission (Box 692)
  - Conn[ecticut] Fulbright Comm[ission] (Box 692)
  - Governor’s Military Staff (Box 692)
  - Greater Hartford Bridge Authority (Box 692)
  - Health, State Department of (Box 692)
  - Israel Putnam Camp Grounds, Citizens Advisory Committee on the Preservation and Maintenance of the (Box 692)
  - Liquor Control Commission (Box 692)
  - Mental Health (Box 692)
  - Mental Retardation Council (Box 692)
  - The following files of appointed posts date around 1954-1955.
  - Agriculture (Box 693)
  - Athletic (Box 693)
  - Banking (Box 693)
  - Chauffeur (Box 693)
  - Commerce, Dep[artmen]t of (Box 693)
  - Governor’s Staff Recommendations (Box 693)
  - Health (Box 693)
  - Highway (Box 693)
  - Insurance (Box 693)
  - Labor [largest file] (Box 693)
  - Milk (Box 693)
  - Motor Vehicles (Box 693)
  - Naval Aid (Box 693)
  - Police (Box 693)
  - Press Secretary (Box 693)
  - Public Utilities (Box 693)
  - Public Works (Box 693)
  - Purchasing (Box 693)
  - State Prison (Box 693)
  - Tax Department, 2 folders (Box 693)
  - Tax Marshall (Box 693)
  - Welfare, 2 folders (Box 693)
  - The following files contain duplicate biographies of appointed commissioners. Those folders marked A.M. may designate that the Governor released the news of their appointments to make the morning newspapers, and P.M. may indicate they were released to make the evening newspapers. One folder labeled "Dunn" contains letters disagreeing with the appointment of Christy Hanas as Welfare Commissioner and supports that of Katherine Dunn.
  - Dunn [Katherine] (Box 694)
  - Joseph Gill A.M. (Box 694)
  - Donald O. Hammerberg A.M. (Box 694)
  - Dennis T. McMahon A.M. (Box 694)
  - Stanley H. Osborne A.M. (Box 694)
  - Henry Pierce, Jr. (Box 694)
  - Thomas J. Spellacy A.M. (Box 694)
  - John Tynan A.M. (Box 694)
  - Newman E. Argraves P.M. (Box 694)
  - Dr. John J. Blasko P.M. (Box 694)
  - Attilio R. Frassinelli P.M. (Box 694)
  - Christy Hanas P.M. (Box 694)
  - Joseph M. Laughlin P.M. (Box 694)
  - Thomas J. Murphy P.M. (Box 694)
  - Renato E. Ricciuti P.M. (Box 694)
  - John L. Sullivan P.M. (Box 694)
- Series 7. Speeches
  This is more than a speech file record series. Folders may contain newspaper clippings, press releases summarizing "Remarks," draft versions, delivered versions, versions of speeches revised afterwards, programs of events, economic and social background on locality, memos re the audience, correspondence with organizers of event, information about the organizers. The handwritten revisions on many versions may be attributed to Gov. Ribicoff.
  Arranged alphabetically by audience or subject. State Archives retained the original order.
  - Accident Prevention Study Dedication, National, Guard Armory, West Hartford, 1960 March 6 (Box 694)
  - Accountants, Waterbury Chapter, Waterbury, 1958 September 11 (Box 694)
  - American Federation of Labor Conn[ecticut] Federation of Labor, Hotel Statler, [Hartford], (First Cong[ressional] District Election), 1956 September 25 (Box 694)
  - Aging, Governor’s Conference on, Hartford, 1958 May 7 (Box 694)
  - Aging, Fifth Annual Conference on, Univ[erstity] of Conn[ecticut], 1957 October 16 (Box 694)
  - Aging, 6th Annual Conference, University of Conn[ecticut], Storrs, 1958 October 8 (Box 694)
  - Albertus Magnus College, Commencement Address, New Haven, 1958 June 5 (Box 694)
  - American Chamber of Commerce, Denver, Colorado, 1969 October 6 (Box 694)
  - Amherst College, 1959 June 14 (Box 694)
  - Ansonia, Maple Street Bridge, 1958 September 22 (Box 694)
  - College of Business and Public Administration, University of Arizona, Tucson, Arizona, 1960 February 27 (Box 694)
  - Automobile M[anu]f[acture]rs Assoc[iation]Detroit, Mich[igan], 1958 April 10 (Box 694)
  - Barre Falls Dam, Barre, Mass[achusetts] (read by W[illia]m Wise), 1956 June 15 (Box 694)
  - Boy Scouts, Stamford, 1956 February 14 (Box 694)
  - Branford Chamber of Commerce, 1958 September 18 (Box 694)
  - Brandeis Foster Alumni, Hotel Statler, Boston, “Education in a Free Society”, 1957 December 1 (Box 694)
  - Bridgeport Rotary Club, “Court Reorganization”, 1958 September 30 (Box 694)
  - Bridgeport, University of – Jacoby Lecture, 1957 February 19 (Box 694)
  - Bridgeport Democratic Town Committee, 1958 October 15 (Box 694)
  - Brown University – Phi Beta Kappa, 1958 March 13 (Box 694)
  - Byram River Bridge, Greenwich, Conn[ecticut] Opening Ceremonies, 1958 October 18 (Box 694)
  - California Trip, Remarks at San Francisco, Los Angeles, 1959 June 18-25 (Box 694)
  - California Newspapermen’s Association – World Newspaper Forum, 1960 October 13 (Box 694)
  - Campaign Speeches, 1958 (Box 694)
  - Campaign Speeches, 1959 (Box 694)
  - Conn[ecticut] Chiefs of Police Academy, Bethany, Conn[ecticut], 1960 April 4-29 (Box 694)
  - Conn[ecticut] Child Study & Treatment Home, Hamden, Conn[ecticut], 1957 July 2 (Box 694)
  - Children and Youth, White House Conference on, 1960 April 27 (Box 694)
  - Civil Defense Home Preparedness, Hall of the House, State Capitol, 1959 December 7 (Box 694)
  - Civil Defense, “Operation Alert”, 1956 July20-1959 April 17 (Box 694)
  - Coffin, Vincent Brown, Inauguration of, Univ[ersity] of H[ar]tf[or]d, 1959 April 21 (Box 694)
  - South Congregational Church, Hartford, 1960 October 19 (Box 694)
  - Conn[ecticut] Assoc[iation] of Boards of Education, 1959 September 18 (Box 694)
  - Connecticut Auto[mobile] Trades Assoc[iation], 1959 November 9 (Box 694)
  - Connecticut Building Congress Annual Meeting, Cheshire, Conn[ecticut], 1958 October 22 (Box 694)
  - Connecticut College Alumnae Day, Fiftieth Anniversary of, New London, 1958 October 4 (Box 694)
  - Conn[ecticut] Education Ass[ociatio]n Convention, Waterbury, 1957 October 25 (Box 694)
  - Connecticut Education Association Annual Conv[ention], Univ[ersity] of Conn[ecticut], Storrs, 1958 October 24 (Box 694)
  - State Employees Assoc[iation] (Connecticut) 17th Annual Convention, Hartford, Conn[ecticut], 1958 October 19 (Box 694)
  - State Employees – Annual Convention of Council 16, State, County and Municipal Employees (AFL – CIO), Hartford, 1958 September 21 (Box 694)
  - State Employees In Service Training Ceremonies, 1960 May 18 (Box 694)
  - Conn[ecticut] Society of Civil Engineers, Cheshire, 1958 March 18 (Box 694)
  - Conn[ecticut] Farm Forum, 1956 November 17 (Box 694)
  - Fire Prevention, 1960 May 28 (Box 694)
  - Fire Prevention Conference, 1956 March 1 (Box 694)
  - Fire Prevention (Box 694)
  - Connecticut General Dedication, 1957 September 11 (Box 694)
  - Community Development Conference [sponsored by the Connecticut Home Builders Association], 1959 November 12 (Box 694)
  - Conn[ecticut] State Labor Council Convention, Hartford, 1958 September 8 (Box 694)
  - Connecticut Medical Service cornerstone laying ceremonies, New Haven, 1957 September 5 (Box 694)
  - Conn[ecticut] Public Expenditure Council, 1960 May 18 (Box 694)
  - Connecticut Public Expenditure Council, 1956 June 6 (Box 694)
  - Conn[ecticut] Sports Writers Alliance Gold Key Award Dinner, Hotel Statler, H[art]f[or]d, 1958 January 27 (Box 694)
  - Conn[ecticut] Sportswriters’ Alliance – (gold key awards), 1957 January 28 (Box 694)
  - Connecticut State Hospital Middletown, 1956 May 15 (Box 694)
  - Dedication of Osborn Division Conn[ecticut] State Prison, Enfield, 1960 September 7 (Box 694)
  - Conn[ecticut] Turnpike Dedication, [I–95], [Greenwich], 1958 January 2 (Box 694)
  - Conservation Conference, Annual, Natural Resources Council of Conn[ecticut], 1959 December 9 (Box 694)
  - Conservation, Conf[erence] on, Natural Resources Council, Hotel Bond, H[art]f[or]d, 1958 January 14 (Box 694)
  - Constitutional Convention, Third Conn[ecticut] State Labor Council, 1959 September 10 (Box 694)
  - Credit Men, (Joint Conference of), Cheshire, Conn[ecticut], 1958 September 17 (Box 694)
  - Credit Union Celebration 50th Anniversary, Hotel Statler, Boston, 1959 May 7 (Box 694)
  - Danbury Chamber of Commerce, 1958 May 14 (Box 694)
  - Delaware, Wilmington, Highway Observance Day, 1960 April 4 (Box 694)
  - Development Conference, State Development Commission, Waverly Inn, Cheshire, 1960 May 23 (Box 694)
  - First Selectmen’s Assoc[iation] of Fairfield County, 1960 May 5 (Box 694)
  - Fairfield State Hospital, 1956 June 19 (Box 694)
  - Future Farmers of America Fair, Durham, Conn[ecticut], 1958 August 2 (Box 694)
  - General Assembly Interim Message, [Farewell Speech], 1961 January 4 (Box 694)
  - [General Assembly –] Budget Message, 1959 February 17 (Box 694)
  - General Assembly – Inaugural Address, 1959 January 7 (Box 694)
  - General Assembly – Closing, 1959 June 3 (Box 694)
  - General Assembly – Special Session – Unemployment – Opening, 1958 March 4 (Box 694)
  - General Assembly – Closing, 1957 June 5 (Box 694)
  - General Assembly – Budget Message, 1957 February 13 (Box 694)
  - General Assembly – Interim Message to the 1957 Session, 1957 January 9 (Box 694)
  - [General Assembly –] Budget Message, 1955 (Box 694)
  - General Assembly Inaugural Address, 1955 January 5 (Box 694)
  - General Assembly – Regular Session Closing, 1955 June 9 (Box 694)
  - General Assembly – Special Session Opening, 1955 June 22 (Box 694)
  - General Assembly – Special Flood Session Closing, 1955 December 15 (Box 694)
  - General Assembly – Special [Flood] Session [Opening], 1955 November 9 (Box 694)
  - General Assembly of the States, 13th Biennial Meeting Edgewater Beach, Chicago, 1956 December 6 (Box 694)
  - Greater [American] Weeklies Assoc[iation] Inc., Hotel Governor Clinton, New Jersey, 1956 May 4 (Box 694)
  - Hamilton Standard, 1957 October 29 (Box 694)
  - Employment of the Handicapped, Regional Meeting of the President’s Commission on, 1958 May 27 (Box 694)
  - Hartford Chamber of Commerce Symposium on “Responsibility of Private Ind[ustrie]s in Urban Renewal (Hotel Statler), 1960 October 19 (Box 694)
  - Hartford Bridge Authority, Greater, re: Tolls Manchester, Conn[ecticut], 1958 September 10 (Box 694)
  - Hat Corporation of America Salesmen, Norwalk, 1958 February 27 (Box 694)
  - Highway Safety Conference August 12, 1960 Hall of the House [Connecticut] (Chiefs of Police, Selectmen & Mayors) (Box 694)
  - Housing and Redevelopment Officials, Conn[ecticut] Assoc[iation] of, Annual State Conference, Northford, Conn[ecticut, 1958 September 19 (Box 694)
  - Industrial Realtors’ Meeting in Chicago (arranged by Conn[ecticut] Development Comm[ission]), 1958 May 2 (Box 694)
  - Industrial Tour, (Yankee Drover Inn, Newtown), 1956 May 16 (Box 694)
  - Industrial Association of the Lower Naugatuck Valley, 1957 December 13 (Box 694)
  - Industrial Tour, 1957 June 11-12 (Box 694)
  - Industrial Tour, 1956 May 16 (Box 694)
  - Industrial Tour, Old Saybrook, Castle Hotel, 1959 May 12 (Box 694)
  - Industry Los Angeles and San Francisco, 1959 June (Box 694)
  - Italian-American War Veterans, Hotel Statler, 1957 August 16 (Box 694)
  - Jackson-Jefferson Day Dinner, Hotel Statler, [Hartford], 1958 March 8 (Box 694)
  - Jackson-Jefferson Day Dinner, New Hampshire, 1959 October 24 (Box 694)
  - Jewitt City – Kickoff to Campaign, 1958 September 2 (Box 694)
  - Kaman Aircraft, Bl[oo]mf[ie]ld, Groundbreaking Ceremonies for new Adm[inistration] & Eng[inee]r B[ui]ld[in]g, 1958 March 24 (Box 694)
  - Kiwanis Clubs of New England – Award to Governor, 1957 September 6 (Box 694)
  - Judicial Conference of Magistrates, Trenton, N[ew] J[ersey], 1959 November 13 (Box 694)
  - Before Judiciary Sub Committee [U.S. Congress] (Box 694)